Guide to the Music Department Records: Series 3, Concert Programs, 1863-[ongoing]
Music Department Records: Series 3, Concert Programs, 1863-[ongoing]
- Series 3. Concert Programs, 1878-[ongoing]
  - General Concerts
    - September 11, 1997: Navaratri 1997: A Concert of South Indian Music, performed by Vaduvur S. N. R. Krishnamurthi, Kovilur K. G. Somanathan, Tanjavur T. R. Govindarajan, B. M. Sundaram (Box 6)
    - September 13, 1997: Navaratri 1997: A Concert of South Indian Music, performed by T. Viswanathan, H. V. Srivatsan, Ramnad Raghavan, Trichy Sankaran, Josepha Cormack, Vasant Venkatachlam (Box 6)
    - September 14, 1997: Navaratri 1997: A Concert of South Indian Music, performed by P. Unnikrishnan, H. V. Srivatsan, Trichy Sankaran (Box 6)
    - September 17, 1997: Navaratri 1997: Bharata Natyam: South Indian Classical Dance, performed by Lakshmi Knight, Anirudda Knight, S. Vidya, Usha Sivakumar, Josepha Cormack, T. Viswanathan, Douglas Knight (Box 6)
    - September 18, 1997: Navaratri 1997: The Masked Goddess in the Mirror, performed by David Schulman (Box 6)
    - October 3, 1997: Lee Luvisi, performed by Lee Luvisi (Box 6)
    - October 4, 1997: Recent Works, performed by Alvin Lucier, et al. (Box 6)
    - October 5, 1997: Bring to Life Operetta Romance in Serenade, performed by Priscilla Gale, Thomas Poole, Mel Strauss (Box 6)
    - October 14, 1997: Forward Kwenda & Erica Azim: Mbira Music of Zimbabwe, performed by Forward Kwenda, Erica Azim (Box 6)
    - October 15, 1997: Twentieth-Century Chamber Music, performed by Libby Van Cleve, Garret Bennett, Penney Kembell, Sarah Meneely-Kyder, Peter Standaart (Box 6)
    - October 17, 1997: Joruri: Music of the Bunraku Puppet Theatre, performed by Various (Box 6)
    - Undated: Padam: Vemaru Cerukuna, performed by Various (Box 6)
    - November 1, 1997: A Program of Music by Ludwig van Beethoven, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Melvin Strauss (Box 6)
    - November 2, 1997: The Music of Lennie Tristano, performed by Adam Roberts, Jackson Moore, Andre Vida, Mike Szeckely, Anthony Braxton (Box 6)
    - November 7-9, 1997: Schubert & Brahms Keyboard Extravaganza, performed by Various (Box 6)
    - November 14, 1997: More Songs from the Song of Solomon, performed by Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce, Phyllis Bruce, Timothy Olson, Wesleyan String Quartet (Box 6)
    - November 17, 1997: Center for the Arts, performed by Anthony Braxton, et al. (Box 6)
    - November 18, 1997: Center for the Arts, performed by James Fei, Jonathan Zorn, Anthony Braxton (Box 6)
    - November 21, 1997: Irish Music, performed by Donna Long, Colm Gannon, Jesse Smith (Box 6)
    - November 23, 1997: Renaissance Soul Revival, performed by Various (Box 6)
    - December 4, 1997: Javanese Music and Dance, performed by I. M. Harjito, Sumarsam, Urip Sri Maeny Sumarsam, Denni Harjito, et al. (Box 6)
    - December 5, 1997: An Evening of American Song, performed by Sanford Sylvan, David Breitman (Box 6)
    - December 6, 1997: Wesleyan University Orchestra and Concert Choir, performed by Priscilla Gale, David Barron (Box 6)
    - December 10, 1997: The Wesleyan Klezmer and Yiddish Music Ensemble, performed by Hankus Netsky, et al. (Box 6)
    - December 12, 1997: West African Drumming and Dance, performed by Abraham Adzenyah, Martin Obeng, Helen Mensah, et al. (Box 6)
    - December 13-14, 1997: Wesleyan Singers, performed by Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce, Ronald Ebrecht, Robert Nasta (Box 6)
    - January 25, 1998: A Piano Recital, performed by Estela Kersenbaum Olevsky, Marjorie Melnick (Box 6)
    - January 30, 1998: The New Talking Drums, performed by The New Talking Drums (Box 6)
    - February 1, 1998: The New World Consort, performed by The New World Consort, Roy Wiseman (Box 6)
    - February 7, 8, and March 1, 1998: New Music Mini-Fest, performed by Various (Box 6)
    - February 13, 1998: Tony Trischka, performed by Tony Trischka, Jeff Berman, Larry Cohen, Kenny Kosek, Barry Mitterhoff, Brenda Presley (Box 6)
    - February 14, 1998: A Valentine of American Song, performed by Phyllis Bruce, Neely Bruce, Martha Hanen, John Basinger, Peter Standaart (Box 6)
    - February 15, 1998: Graduate Recital: Elizabeth Sayre, performed by Elizabeth Sayre, et al. (Box 6)
    - February 20, 1998: Young Organ Virtuosi, performed by Joel Bacon, Lei Ray Yu, Tom Trenney (Box 6)
    - February 22, 1998: Chamber Music Recital, performed by Chai-Lun Yueh, Sarah Meneely Kyder (Box 6)
    - February 27, 1998: A Tone (Thom) For Your Sins: A Masters Thesis Recital by Susan Tveekrem, performed by Susan Tveekrem, et al. (Box 6)
    - February 28, 1998: Brahms, Griffes, Jonas, Faure, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Melvin Strauss, Edward Jessen, Chris Jonas (Box 6)
    - Undated: Inspiration Across Cultures, performed by Ernest Boamah (Box 6)
    - March 1, 1998: Harpsichordist Britt Wheeler: Works by Bach and Scarlatti, performed by Britt Wheeler (Box 6)
    - March 1, 1998: Works of David Tudor, performed by John Driscoll, Matt Rogalsky, John D. S. Adams, Ron Kuivila (Box 6)
    - March 28, 1998: Piano Concerti, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Melvin Strauss, Grace Kim, Kevin Shihoten, Nathan Patterson (Box 6)
    - April 2, 1998: Electric Sky Church: Senior Thesis Recital, performed by Steve McPherson, et al. (Box 6)
    - April 3, 1998: Manhattan String Quartet, performed by Eric Lewis, John Dexter, Kenneth Freed, Chris Finckel, Okon Hwang (Box 6)
    - April 4, 1998: Saint Matthew Passion, performed by Neely Bruce, Manchester Symphony Orchestra, Wesleyan Singers, Middlesex Community Children's Choir, et al. (Box 6)
    - April 7, 1998: Masked/Unmasked, performed by Guillermo E. Brown, et al. (Box 6)
    - April 8, 1998: A Journey Through the African Diaspora, performed by Ayanda Clarke, John Speck, Djembe Orchestra, Exe Ensemble (Box 6)
    - Undated: Uzbek Piano Prodigies of the Uspensky Music Conservatory, performed by Various (Box 6)
    - Undated: Daedalus & Draupadi: Fate and Invention, performed by Gregory Acker, et al. (Box 6)
    - April 17, 1998: Center of the Arts, performed by Anthony Braxton, et al. (Box 6)
    - April 18, 1998: Center of the Arts, performed by Anthony Braxton, et al. (Box 6)
    - April 18, 1998: The Elizabeth Verveer Tishler Piano Competition: Recital of the Finalists of 1998, performed by Various (Box 6)
    - April 18, 1998: Senior Recital, performed by Anil Seth (Box 6)
    - April 18, 1998: Center of the Arts, performed by Anthony Braxton, et al. (Box 6)
    - April 22, 1998:, performed by (Box 6)
    - April 23, 1998: Ronald Ebrecht: University Organist, performed by Ronald Ebrecht (Box 6)
    - April 25, 1998: Program, performed by Wesleyan Small Jazz Ensemble, Christopher Jonas, Wesleyan Percussion Ensemble, Jay Hoggard, et al. (Box 6)
    - May 1, 1998: Evident Maps: Choral Works of Five Contemporary Composers on Themes of Belief and Matter, performed by Wesleyan University Concert Choir, Neely Bruce (Box 6)
    - May 3, 1998: The Wesleyan University Orchestra: Farewell Concert to Melvin Strauss, performed by The Wesleyan University Orchestra, Melvin Strauss, et al. (Box 6)
    - May 6, 1998: The Wesleyan Klezmer and Yiddish Music Ensemble, performed by Wesleyan Klezmer, Yiddish Music Ensemble, Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce (Box 6)
    - Undated: Unleashed Rhythm: Percussion from Cameroon / An American Experiment, performed by Jessie Torrisi, Dan Gilbert, et al. (Box 6)
    - May 7, 1998: Senior Recital: Sunshine Vogt, performed by Sunshine Vogt, et al. (Box 6)
    - May 7, 1998: Hymn to Matter, performed by Edward Jessen, et al. (Box 6)
    - May 9, 1998: Ernest Boamah: Pianist/Composer, performed by Ernest Boamah (Box 6)
    - October 23, 1998: The Wall Street Chamber Players, performed by The Wall Street Chamber Players (Box 6)
    - October 24, 1998: Twenty-Five Years of Music at the Center for the Arts, performed by Various (Box 6)
    - November 6, 1998: New Orleans Klezmer All-Stars, performed by Glenn Hartman, Robert Wagner, David Rebeck, Jonathan Freilich, Arthur Kastler, Kevin O'Day (Box 6)
    - November 8, 1998: Little Three Choral Festival, performed by The Amherst College Concert Choir, Mallorie Chernin, The Williams College Chamber Choir, E. Wayne Abercrombie, Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce (Box 6)
    - November 11, 1998: Tute Chigamba, performed by Tute Chigamba (Box 6)
    - November 13, 1998: Wesleyan Singers with Special Guests the Wesleyan Spirits, performed by Wesleyan Singers, Wesleyan Spirits, Neely Bruce (Box 6)
    - November 14, 1998: Music for a Centenary, performed by Wes U. Orch. (Box 6)
    - November 15, 1998: Carver Blanchard, Lute, performed by Carver Blanchard (Box 6)
    - November 18, 1998: Small Ensemble, performed by Anthony Braxton, et al. (Box 6)
    - November 19, 1998: Voice Master Class with Julianne Baird, performed by Julianne Baird, Neely Bruce (Box 6)
    - November 20, 1998: Soprano Julianne Baird, Fortepiano Malcolm Bilson, performed by Julianne Baird, Malcolm Bilson (Box 6)
    - November 21, 1998: Large Ensemble, performed by Anthony Braxton, et al. (Box 6)
    - December 5, 1998: Candlelight Concert 1998, performed by Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce, Ronald Ebrecht, et al. (Box 6)
    - December 7, 1998: Recording Art, performed by Michael J. Rogers, Neely Bruce, Ron Quivila (Box 6)
    - December 9, 1998: The Spirit of Bessarabia, performed by The Wesleyan Klezmer Ensemble, Hankus Netsky, Cantor Morton Shames (Box 6)
    - December 10, 1998: An Evening of Javanese Gamelan and Dance, performed by Wesleyan Gamelan Ensemble, Kyai Pradhah, Kyai Mentul (Box 6)
    - December 11, 1998: An Evening of West African Drumming, performed by Abraham K. Adzenyah, Helen Mensah (Box 6)
    - December 12, 1998: Wesleyan University Orchestra, performed by Angel Gil-Ordonez, Neely Bruce (Box 6)
    - February 2, 1999: The Late Show 2.0, performed by Mike Heffley, Chris Jonas, et al. (Box 6)
    - February 9, 1999: Bregman Electro-Acoustic Music Graduate Program at Dartmouth College, performed by Various (Box 6)
    - February 16, 1999: The Late Show IV, performed by Various (Box 6)
    - Undated: The Rock Star, performed by Various (Box 6)
    - March 26, 1999: Spring Along the Rhein and the Seine, performed by Jill Riggles, Peter Standaart (Box 6)
    - March 28, 1999: Senior Honors Thesis Recital, performed by Kareem A. George, Bernard Phillips, Mitchell Vines (Box 6)
    - March 28, 1999: A Ragtime Centennial: Elite Syncopation, performed by Liz Smith, Perry Elliot, Ettie Luckey, Roy Wiseman, Gary Chapman (Box 6)
    - April 2, 1999: Senior Thesis Recital: Improvisation within Structure, performed by Daniel Koulomzin (Box 6)
    - April 3, 1999: Blue Chevy Songbook, performed by Blue Chevy Singers, Aaron Weiss (Box 6)
    - April 3, 1999: Original and Not So Original Compositions, performed by Demian Mason, Martin Lijtmaer, et al. (Box 6)
    - April 4, 1999: South Indian Music, performed by Abhishek Raghuraman, Ananthakrishnan, Palghat Raghu, A. Anand (Box 6)
    - Undated: oriGINal coMpoStiOns of mUsic aND laNguAgE, performed by Seth Delinger (Box 6)
    - April 9, 1999: Nathan Patterson Senior Thesis Recital, performed by Nathan Patterson, et al. (Box 6)
    - April 9, 1999: Mingus and Me, performed by Paul S. Stewart, et al. (Box 6)
    - April 10, 1999: Digging in the Dirt: A Synthesis of West African Traditional and Popular Music, performed by Michael L. Buescher (Box 6)
    - April 10, 1999: Kevin Uehlinger: Senior Recital, performed by Kevin Uehlinger, et al. (Box 6)
    - April 10, 1999: Evoloution: Original Compositions Exploring the Idioms of Jazz, Blues, Funk, Soul & Hip Hop, performed by Kabir Sen, et al. (Box 6)
    - April 11, 1999: Wesleyan Singers, performed by Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce, Abraham Adzenyah, Hopewell Concert Choir, et al. (Box 6)
    - April 17, 1999: John Kamitsuka, Pianist, performed by John Kamitsuka (Box 6)
    - April 22, 1999: Ronald Ebrecht, University Organist, performed by Ronald Ebrecht (Box 6)
    - April 23, 1999: Music and Dance from Mali, Guinea, Senegal, and the Gambia, performed by Wesleyan Mande Music Ensemble (Box 6)
    - April 24, 1999: Hymn to Joy, performed by The Wesleyan University Orchestra, Angel Gil-Ordonez, Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce, et al. (Box 6)
    - April 28, 1999: Wesleyan Klezmer Ensemble Spring Concert, performed by Wesleyan Klezmer Ensemble, Hankus Netsky, Mel Mercier (Box 6)
    - April 30 and May 1, 1999: Duke Ellington's Sacred Concert: A Centennial Celebration, performed by Wesleyan Jazz Orchestra, Jay Hoggard, Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce (Box 6)
    - Undated: The Late Show Gets Early, performed by Various (Box 6)
    - May 8, 1999: Wayang Kulit, performed by The Wesleyan Gamelan Ensemble, I. M. Harjito, Sumarsam (Box 6)
    - June 29, 1999: Summer at the Center Noontime Concert: A Commemoration of Chopin (Part 1 of 2), performed by Neely Bruce (Box 6)
    - June 30, 1999: Summer at the Center Noontime Concert: A Commemoration of Chopin (Part 2 of 2), performed by Neely Bruce (Box 6)
    - July 27, 1999: South Indian Vina, performed by Vijayasree Mokkapati, Ramnad V. Raghavan, Joseph Getter (Box 6)
    - September 9, 1999: Navaratri 1999: A Concert of South Indian Music, performed by T. Viswanathan, Ramnad Raghavan, David Nelson (Box 7)
    - September 10, 1999: Navaratri 1999: A Concert of North Indian Music, performed by Kartik Seshadri, Arup Chatterjee (Box 7)
    - September 11, 1999: Navaratri 1999: Bharata Natyam (South Indian Classical Dance), performed by Aniruddha Knight, Lakshmi Knight, Josepha Cormack, T. Viswanathan, Susan Tveekrem, Douglas Knight (Box 7)
    - September 17, 1999: Hot Jam!, performed by Hot Jam! (Box 7)
    - October 1, 1999: The Lydian String Quartet, performed by Daniel Stepner, Judith Eissenberg, Mary Ruth, Rhonda Rider (Box 7)
    - October 8, 1999: Experimental Music, performed by Various (Box 7)
    - October 10, 1999: Burning Bush Baroque, performed by Peter Standaart, Libby Van Cleve, Britt Wheeler (Box 7)
    - October 15, 1999: Anton Kuerti, Pianist, performed by Anton Kuerti (Box 7)
    - October 30, 1999: Combinations: An Evening of Chamber Music, performed by Chai-Lun Yueh, Sarah Meneely-Kyder, et al. (Box 7)
    - October 31, 1999: The Spirit's Song: Reflection on All Hallow's Eve, performed by Ann Monoyios, Andrew Appel (Box 7)
    - November 3, 1999: Kakraba Lobi: Gyil Master from Ghana, performed by Kakraba Lobi, Valerie Naranjo (Box 7)
    - Undated: The Wesleyan University Ochestra, Open Rehearsal, performed by The Wesleyan University Ochestra, Jaap Schroeder (Box 7)
    - November 6, 1999: The Atlantis Trio, performed by Enid Sutherland, Jaap Schroeder, Penelope Crawford (Box 7)
    - November 8, 1999: The Baltic Philharmonic Chamber Orchestra, performed by The Baltic Philharmonic Chamber Orchestra, Gudmunder Emilsson, The Brown University Chorus, Frederick Jodry (Box 7)
    - November 10, 1999: Experesiones de Latinos: Born of this Millenium Ascending into the Next, performed by Eduardo Tancredi, Gilberto Rivera, Yolanda Melendez, Daniel Viggiani, Flavia Steiner-Biggian (Box 7)
    - November 12-14, 1999: Keyboard Music of Chopin and Mendelssohn: A Mini-Fesitval of Early Nineteenth-Century Music, performed by Various (Box 7)
    - December 3, 1999: Music from Mali Guinea, Senegal, and the Gambia, performed by Wesleyan Mande Music Ensemble, Eric Charry, Ayanda Clarke, Papa Ladji Camara (Box 7)
    - December 4, 1999: Snow White / Topeng, performed by I. Nymoan Catra, Holy Cross College's new Balinese Gamelan Orchestra, Andrew McGraw (Box 7)
    - December 4, 1999: Candlelight Concert: Handel's Messiah, Part I, performed by The Wesleyan Singers, Ronald Ebrecht, Wesleyan Chamber Players (Box 7)
    - December 7, 1999: Shirts & Skin, performed by Tim Miller, John Carr, Doug Sadownick (Box 7)
    - December 10, 1999: West African Drumming and Dance, performed by Abraham Adzenyah, Helen Mensah, Martin Obeng (Box 7)
    - December 10, 1999: Roamin' Holiday - A View from A Broad by Pat Oleszko, performed by Pat Oleszko (Box 7)
    - December 11, 1999: Wesleyan University Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Angel Gil-Ordonez (Box 7)
    - Undated: A Capella Concert, performed by The Spirits, The MazelTones, The New Group, The Cardinal Sinners, Quasimodal (Box 7)
    - January 30, 2000: The Deborah Strauss & Jeff Warschauer Duo, performed by Deborah Strauss, Jeff Warschauer (Box 7)
    - January 30, 2000: In My Garden: Yiddish Songs and Music of Love and Rejoicing, performed by Deborah Strauss, Jeff Warschauer (Box 7)
    - February 4, 2000: Gabriela Granados and the Wesleyan Ensemble of the Americas, performed by Gabriela Granados, Sasha Morena Caponi, Anna Cristina Moore, Jose Valle Fajardo, Wesleyan Ensemble of the Americas (Box 7)
    - February 12, 2000: Young Organ Virtuosi at Wesleyan: Chamber Music Program I, performed by Various (Box 7)
    - February 13, 2000: Young Organ Virtuosi at Wesleyan: Chamber Music Program II, performed by Various (Box 7)
    - Undated: Wesleyan University Orchestra, Joined by the Middletown Creative Orchestra Program for Open Rehearsal, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Middletown Creative Orchestra, Angel Gil-Ordonez (Box 7)
    - February 15, 2000: Jens Brand: Performance/Installation, performed by Jens Brand (Box 7)
    - February 19, 2000: Healing Music from Africa, performed by Jay Hoggard, Kwaku Martin Obeng, et al. (Box 7)
    - February 24, 2000: The 2000 Annie Sonnenblick Lecture, performed by President Douglas J. Bennet (Box 7)
    - February 25, 2000: Experimental Music, performed by Jason Cady, Justine Flynn, Matthew Welch (Box 7)
    - February 27, 2000: Jubilee Y2K: For Every Generation, performed by Various (Box 7)
    - February 27, 2000: Twentieth Century Music for Viola Piano, performed by Aaron Westman, Neely Bruce (Box 7)
    - March 1, 2000: The Barton Workshop, performed by Various (Box 7)
    - March 3-4, 2000: Spring Faculty Dance Concert, performed by Various (Box 7)
    - March 4, 2000: Children's Concert, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Angel Gil-Ordonez (Box 7)
    - Undated: Op. 1, performed by John Adamian, et al. (Box 7)
    - March 5, 2000: Andrew Leonard, Guitar, performed by Andrew Leonard (Box 7)
    - March 7, 2000: A Concert of South Indian Music, performed by T. Viswanathan, David Nelson (Box 7)
    - Undated: Matthew Welch - Piping Recital - Wesleyan, performed by Matthew Welch (Box 7)
    - Undated: Possibly Beautiful: A Thesis Concert by Scott Wilson, performed by Scott Wilson, et al. (Box 7)
    - Undated: 12 Sets of 3: 36 Sonic Events for Light and Shadow, performed by Molly Jane Sturges (Box 7)
    - March 30, 2000: A Concert of Original Music, performed by Gregory Tuzzolo, et al. (Box 7)
    - March 31, 2000: New Patterns: AKG13, performed by Alex Kennedy-Grant, et al. (Box 7)
    - March 31 and April 1, 2000: Senior Thesis Dance Concert, performed by Elizabeth Doctors, Sarah P. Rosenberg, Amanda Snyder, Ami Student, Maggie Thom (Box 7)
    - March 31, April 1-2, 2000: Einstein Dreaming, performed by Bex Schwartz, et al. (Box 7)
    - April 2, 2000: Threads of Joy: Senior Recital, performed by Jessica Blinn, Friends (Box 7)
    - April 7, 2000: Steve Lehman's Honors Thesis Concert, performed by Steve Lehman (Box 7)
    - April 7, 2000: Exploring Femininity in Romanticism: Frederic Chopin and Amy Beach, performed by Sadie Danforth, Lydia Rosenthal, Lily Sutton (Box 7)
    - April 8, 2000: Women and Redemption through Love in Eighteenth- and Nineteenth-Century Opera, performed by Meredith Tobias, et al. (Box 7)
    - April 9, 2000: The Musicians, performed by Various (Box 7)
    - April 12, 2000: Carlos Martin Carle: Electric Guitar, performed by Carlos Martin Carle, et al. (Box 7)
    - Undated: Messiaen and Color: Seeing Things as They Are, performed by Unknown (Box 7)
    - Undated: Peter Sax: Repetition and Trance, performed by Peter Sax, et al. (Box 7)
    - Undated: Inexplicable Balance: You Just Never Know How Shit Will Work Out, performed by Paul Josephs, et al. (Box 7)
    - Undated: A Celebration of Chaos, performed by Matty Rahaim, et al. (Box 7)
    - Undated: Senior Honors Thesis Recital, performed by Aaron Westman (Box 7)
    - April 15, 2000: Sasha Bogdanowitsch: An Ocean Walks Behind a Lake, performed by Sasha Bogdanowitsch, Elizabeth Panzer, et al. (Box 7)
    - April 15, 2000: Mabuhay: A Cultural Explosion Talent Showcase, performed by Various (Box 7)
    - April 16, 2000: An Afternoon of Celtic Harp and Fiddle, performed by Maureen Brennan, Brian Theriault (Box 7)
    - April 17, 2000: Center of the Arts, performed by Anthony Braxton, et al. (Box 7)
    - April 18, 2000: Invisible Men, performed by Khary Cuffe, Kwame Ohemeng, et al. (Box 7)
    - Undated: Samsara, performed by Mary Cyriac, Mayuran Tiruchelvam, et al. (Box 7)
    - Undated: Infinite: Taking You Where You Want to Go, performed by Terence Joseph, et al. (Box 7)
    - Undated: Between the Fabric of Every Second: Senior Thesis Concert, performed by Ben Sterling, et al. (Box 7)
    - April 19, 2000: Center of the Arts, performed by Anthony Braxton, et al. (Box 7)
    - April 26, 2000: Contemporary KOTO Music, performed by Ryuoko Mizutani, et al. (Box 7)
    - April 28, 2000: The Wesleyan Millennium Orchestra, performed by The Javanese Gamelan, Wesleyan Jazz Orchestra, Wesleyan University Orchestra, Wesleyan Singers, Wesleyan Wind Ensemble (Box 7)
    - April 29, 2000: Precision Dance Ensemble presents ECHO, performed by Oshadi Kelly, Toni Smith, et al. (Box 7)
    - April 28-30, 2000: The Shoemakers, performed by Mark Sussman, et al. (Box 7)
    - April 29, 2000: An Evening of Jazz with Vocalist Kevin Mahogany and the Wesleyan Jazz Orchestra, performed by Kevin Mahogany, Wesleyan Jazz Orchestra, Jay Hoggard (Box 7)
    - April 30, 2000: I-Pride, performed by Various (Box 7)
    - May 3, 2000: A Celebration of Gerhard Stabler at 50, performed by Tomas Bachli, Paul de Jong, Kunsu Shim, et al. (Box 7)
    - May 5, 2000: Wesleyan Singers, performed by Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce, Meredith Tobias, Ronald Ebrecht, et al. (Box 7)
    - May 5 and 6, 2000: Breaking Something: Spring Dance Concert, performed by Sara Elisa Lesin, Rebecca Milburn, Megan Koss, et al. (Box 7)
    - May 6, 2000: Javanese Music, Dance, and Drama, performed by I. M. Harjito, et al. (Box 7)
    - May 9, 2000: An Evening of Japanese Music, performed by Masayo Ishigure, et al. (Box 7)
    - May 10, 2000: Balinese Kechak Musical Drama, performed by Ni Ketut Suryatini, I Nyoman Cata, et al. (Box 7)
    - May 11, 2000: Student Accordian Recital, performed by Various (Box 7)
    - May 12, 2000: The WPA, performed by John Carr, et al. (Box 7)
    - May 13, 2000: Flute Concert: Shashank Ensemble, performed by Shashank, B. V. Raghavendrarao, N. Ramakrishnan, T. Radhakrishnan, T. Rajashekhar (Box 7)
    - May 13, 2000: Indian Music and Dance Student Recital, performed by Various (Box 7)
    - May 21, 2000: Songs of Fate, performed by The Greater Middletown Chorale, Joseph D-Eugenio, et al. (Box 7)
    - July 26, 2000: Feed Your Soul: A Concert of South Indian Karnatak Music, performed by Joseph Getter, Michael Fogg, Susan Tveekrem (Box 7)
    - September 14, 2002: Near Eastern Music Ensemble, performed by Simon Sasheen, Rima Khcheich, Jamal Sinno, Bassam Saba, William Shaheen, Naijib Shaheen, Michel Merhej (Box 7)
    - September 27, 2002: An Evening of Arabic Music & Dance, performed by Beth Bahia Cohen, Sarra Ibriham, James Samir Ismail, Nicole LeCorgne, Bridget Robbins, Jamal Sinno (Box 7)
    - October 6, 2002: FLUX Quartet, performed by Tom Chiu, Jess Mills, Max Mendel, Darrett Adkins (Box 7)
    - October 10, 2002: John Sinclair and the Billy Pilgrim Ensemble, performed by John Sinclair, Billy Pilgrim Ensemble (Box 7)